130/80. That's a little high.
(Sheldon:)We can attribute that to the stress
of sneaking past the security desk.
(Steph:)Where did you get the stethoscope
and pressure cuff?
(Sheldon:)My Aunt Marion gave them to me
for my 12th birthday.
(Sheldon:)She thought if I failed at theoretical physics
that I should have a trade to fall back on.
(Sheldon:)And by the way, the blood pressure cuff
is called a sphygmomanometer.
(Leonard:)- Thank you.
- Didn't teach you that in medical school?
- I'm kind of busy here.
- I understand.
(Sheldon:)All I need is for you to authorize
these tests.
Ha. A cardiac stress test,
a full-body MRI, an electromyogram...
(Steph:)...a CBC, baseline glucose, upper GI?
Oh, and exploratory laparoscopy.
The last time I had hiccups...
(Sheldon:)...it felt like my diaphragm
was just going through the motions.
(Steph:)Go home, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Can I at least have the upper GI?
(Sheldon:)I already drank the barium.
(Penny:)Oh, hey.